{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"5073","name":"El Cunado Mobile Food Trailer","address":"3700 Central St","zipcode":"4821","owner":"Jessica Lopez","licenseNumber":"038463","licenseType":"Mobile Food Establishment","establishmentType":"LHD - Mobile Food Establishmen","establishmentStatus":"Seasonal","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"395.0","coords":"-83.13171,42.32395","geojson":{"id":"5073","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.131712765,42.323949715]},"properties":{"name":"El Cunado Mobile Food Trailer","owner":"Jessica Lopez","address":"3700 Central St","zipcode":"4821","license_type":"Mobile Food Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"038463","establishmentid":"5073","establishment_type":"LHD - Mobile Food Establishmen","establishment_status":"Seasonal","review_frequency_days":"395.0","most_recent_license_date":"5/29/2019"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"5038","name":"El Cunado Production Kitchen","address":"3700 Central St","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"5210","name":"Black Horse Cantina II","address":"3788 Central St","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"4908","name":"Los Dos Amigo's 2","address":"7115 Parkwood St","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"3288","name":"Los Dos Amigos-1","address":"7115 Parkwood St","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"789","name":"Red Park Inn Bar","address":"4442 Central ","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"51622816","name":"Red Park Inn","address":"4442 Central St","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"515","name":"Holy Cross Council 2739","address":"4381 Larkins St","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"715","name":"Yacht Club Exclusive","address":"7059 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"716","name":"Jordans Family Restaurant","address":"7031 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"4821"},{"establishmentid":"743","name":"Freer Bar","address":"7355 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"4821"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"49162","inspectionDate":"2019-09-19T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.19","violationDescription":"If time only, rather than time in conjunction with temperature, is used as the public health control for a working supply of POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  before cooking, or for READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  that is displayed or held for service for immediate consumption:   \r\n(1)   Written procedures are required to be prepared in advance, maintained in the establishment, and made available to the REGULATORY AUTHORITY upon request.(Pf)\r\n(2)   The FOOD shall be marked to indicate the time that is 4 hrs past the point in which food is removed from temperature control, or 6 hrs if the temperature is maintained below 70Â°F. (Pf)\r\n(3)   Food in unmarked containers or in containers that exceed the time limit are to be discarded. (P)\r\n        \r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Time controlled food(s)","subItem":"potentially hazardous food(s) before cooking","problemDescription":"Without time control mark","subProblem":"","location":"MOBILE UNIT","subLocation":"TIME MARKING","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-10-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide clear easy to read time marks."},{"violationCode":"3-301.11","violationDescription":"(A) To prevent food contamination FOOD EMPLOYEES shall properly wash their      hands.\r\n(B) FOOD EMPLOYEES may not contact exposed, READY-TO-EAT FOOD with      their bare hands and shall use suitable UTENSILS such as deli tissue,       spatulas, tongs, single-use gloves, or dispensing EQUIPMENT. (P)\r\n(C) FOOD EMPLOYEES shall minimize bare hand and arm contact with exposed     FOOD that is not in a READY-TO-EAT form. (Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Ready-to-eat food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Handled with bare hands","subProblem":"","location":"MOBILE UNIT","subLocation":"Bare hand contact","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-10-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Suitable utensils or single-use gloves are to be utilized."},{"violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\r\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \r\n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\r\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \r\n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Pest(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Present in facility","subProblem":"","location":"MOBILE UNIT","subLocation":"PESTS","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-10-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove pests from facility."},{"violationCode":"5-501.15","violationDescription":"(A) Receptacles and waste handling units for REFUSE, recyclables, and returnables used with materials containing FOOD residue and used outside the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT shall be designed and constructed to have tight-fitting lids, doors, or covers.\r\n(B) Receptacles and waste handling units for REFUSE and recyclables such as an on-site compactor shall be installed so that accumulation of debris and insect and rodent attraction and harborage are minimized and effective cleaning is facilitated around and, if the unit is not installed flush with the base pad, under the unit.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Waste receptacle(s)","subItem":"recyclable/returnable container","problemDescription":"With doors,lids or covers","subProblem":"Not provided","location":"OUTSIDE PREMISES","subLocation":"Lid(s)/cover(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2019-10-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"6-202.15","violationDescription":"Outer openings of a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT shall be protected against the entry of insects and rodents. Unless otherwise allowed by law. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Outer opening(s)","subItem":"door(s)","problemDescription":"Not provided with","subProblem":"Screening that is sixteen mesh to the inch or greater","location":"BACK DOOR","subLocation":"Openings","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2019-10-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to meet requirements above."},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\r\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\r\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Certified Manager","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"45152","inspectionDate":"2019-02-15T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-302.12","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be provided and readily accessible for use in ensuring attainment and maintenance of FOOD temperatures as specified under Chapter 3. (Pf)   \r\n(B) A TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE with a suitable small-diameter probe that is designed to measure the temperature of thin masses shall be provided and readily accessible to accurately measure the temperature in thin FOODS such as MEAT patties and FISH filets. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food thermometer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not available","subProblem":"","location":"THERMOMETER","subLocation":"Thermometer(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-03-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Make available at all times."},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\r\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\r\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Missing","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Certified Manager","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"6-301.14","violationDescription":"A sign or poster that notifies FOOD EMPLOYEES to wash their hands shall be provided at all HANDWASHING SINKS used by FOOD EMPLOYEES and shall be clearly visible to FOOD EMPLOYEES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Handwashing signage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"Hand washing signage","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provided handwashing signage "}]},{"inspectionid":"37746","inspectionDate":"2016-09-07T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"MOBILE UNIT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-09-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"4-302.12","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be provided and readily accessible for use in ensuring attainment and maintenance of FOOD temperatures as specified under Chapter 3. (Pf)   \r\n(B) A TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE with a suitable small-diameter probe that is designed to measure the temperature of thin masses shall be provided and readily accessible to accurately measure the temperature in thin FOODS such as MEAT patties and FISH filets. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food thermometer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"MOBILE UNIT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-09-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"4-204.112","violationDescription":"(A)  In a mechanically refrigerated or hot FOOD storage unit, the sensor of a TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE shall be located to measure the air temperature in the warmest part of a mechanically refrigerated unit and in the coolest part of a hot FOOD storage unit.\r\n(B)  Cold or hot holding EQUIPMENT used for POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD shall be designed to include and shall be equipped with at least one integral or permanently affixed TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE that is located to allow easy viewing of the device's temperature display (EXCEPT, heat lamps, cold plates, steam tables, or other equipment where it is not practical).\r\n(C)  TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be designed to be easily readable.\r\n(D)  FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES and water TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES on WAREWASHING machines shall have a numerical scale, printed record, or digital readout in increments no greater than 1C or 2F in the intended range of use. (Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Thermometer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"MOBILE UNIT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-09-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Non-food contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"MOBILE UNIT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"3-304.12","violationDescription":"During pauses in FOOD preparation or dispensing, UTENSILS shall be stored:\r\n(A) In the FOOD with their handles above the top of the FOOD and the container;\r\n(B) In FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS with their handles above the      top of the FOOD within containers or EQUIPMENT that can be closed, such as      bins of sugar, flour, or cinnamon;\r\n(C) On a clean portion of the FOOD preparation table or cooking EQUIPMENT\r\n(D)  In running water, such as dipper well.\r\n(E)  In a clean, protected location if the UTENSILS, such as ice scoops, are   used only with a FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS; or\r\n(F)  In a container of water maintained at a temperature of at least 135Â° F.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Dispensing utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly stored","subProblem":"","location":"MOBILE UNIT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2016-09-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Relocate."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2019-10-31T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"5073"}}